Toggle navigation [ ](https://www.trafficwave.net/index.html)

    * #### How Can You Use AutoResponders?
        
        See how TrafficWave.net Email Marketing helps these industries...

TrafficWave.net Privacy Policy
==============================

TrafficWave.net Privacy Policy
------------------------------

### What Does TrafficWave Do With My Information?

At TrafficWave.net. (referred throughout as “TrafficWave”, “We”, “Us” or “Our”), we respect your privacy and take protecting it seriously. This Privacy Policy covers our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website and service, www.trafficwave.net owned and operated by Hamney Roobright, Inc. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which our Customers have engaged us.

Here's what we do - and, more importantly, don't do - with any information you provide us.

#### “I Am A Subscriber To An Email List Managed Through TrafficWave.net.”

Your email address, name and any other information you provide, such as address and phone number you provide to our Customers, are held in strict confidence. We only keep your information so that our Customer, whose email list you subscribed to, can email you.

We do not contact you. We do not sell or share your information with anyone else.

We collect information under the direction of our Customers, and have no direct relationship with you, whose personal data we process. We work with our Customers to help them provide notice to their subscribers concerning the purpose for which personal information is collected.

If you are a subscriber of one of our Customers and would no longer like to be contacted by our Customer, please contact our Customer that you interact with directly.

We acknowledge that you have the right to access, amend, or request the removal of your personal information at any time. To that end, you may use the links that are provided in the footer of each message sent via TrafficWave.net to accomplish this. In the event that you feel that your personal information was obtained and used in the TrafficWave.net system without your permission, you may indicate this concern within the same link used to request removal.

An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data outside of the systems and networks controlled/managed by TrafficWave.net should direct his or her query to our Customer (the data controller).

TrafficWave.net exercises no control whatsoever over the content of the information passing through TrafficWave.net servers. All subscriber data generated by Customer are held in strict confidence. This data is never released by TrafficWave.net to any other parties for any purpose, and is only processed on TrafficWave.net's servers as required in the delivery of email message content provided and scheduled by our Customer, and to provide analytical feedback data such as open rates, click-through data, etc…

We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Customers for as long as needed in order to provide services to our Customers. We will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### “I Am A TrafficWave Customer.”

All account information for our Customers is held in strict confidence.

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell or share your information with anyone. We only collect information like your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and billing information so we can provide the email marketing services described on our website.

You will receive our regular training and support emails as part of our ongoing training and support. To opt out of these training and support emails, you will want to close your account from within your TrafficWave.net Members Area.

##### Service Related Emails

We may also send you service related email announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. You do not have an option to opt out of these emails, which are not promotional in nature.

##### Service Providers

We use other third parties, such as a credit card processing company, to bill you for services. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personal information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

##### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings or similar legal process, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

##### Access To Personal Information

Upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change in your Members Area or by contacting us at the address below. We will respond to your request within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

##### Security

The security of your personal information and our customers' information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information, such as login credentials and credit card information, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us directly.

#### “I Am Also A TrafficWave Affiliate...”

Your name, address, phone and fax number, email address, tax ID number or SSN and any other information you provide are held in strict confidence. We collect this information only so we can generate your commission checks and meet United States federal tax requirements. We do not sell or share your information with anyone else.

#### What About Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies?

##### What are Cookies?

Cookies are small pieces of text sent by your web browser by our website. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows us, our partners, affiliates, and other service providers to recognize you and make your next visit easier and our service more useful to you.

##### How TrafficWave Uses Cookies

We and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or services providers use technologies, such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer our website, tracking users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. All cookies contain coded fragments specific and useful only to the functionality of our internal systems. No discernible personal information or data can be directly extracted by others from any cookie generated by TrafficWave.net.

##### Your choices regarding TrafficWave cookies

You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited. If you'd like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.

#### What About Log Files?

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to analyze trends, administer our website, track visitors' movements around our website, and gather demographic information about our visitors as a whole. We do link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about our website visitors.

#### Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our website, which may contain personal information. We do obtain our customers' consent to post their name along with their testimonial via email prior to posting the testimonial on our website. However, if you wish to request the removal of your testimonial, please contact us.

#### Social Media Features

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button. These features may collect your IP address and the page you are visiting on our website. It may also set a cookie to enable the features to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### Notification Of Privacy Policy Changes

We may update our privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes, we will notify you or our customer by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on our website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### Links To Other Sites

Our website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourages you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by our website.

#### Public Forums

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.. Contact Us

##### If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via email at admin@trafficwave.net or via postal mail at

Hamney Roobright, Inc.  
330 Rayford Rd PMB 312  
Spring TX 77386  
admin@trafficwave.net

_This policy was last updated on May 24, 2018 and supersedes all previous versions._  

###### HOME

###### ARTICLES

###### OTHER

Copyright © 2000- All Rights Reserved.  
TrafficWave.net  
330 Rayford Rd #312  
Spring TX 77386
